{
  "title": "Derivative Proficiency F2019 V2",
  "questions": [

{
  "question": "Compute $j'(x)$ if $j(x)=x^4 \\sec(x)$.",
  "answer": "4x^3\\sec(x) + x^4\\sec(x)\\tan(x)",
  "ivar": "x"
},

{
  "question": "Compute $P'(\\theta)$ if $P(\\theta)=\\sin(3\\theta^5 -2\\theta +1)$",
  "answer": "\\cos(3\\theta^5 -2\\theta +1)*(15\\theta^4-2)",
  "ivar": "Î¸"
},


{
  "question": "Compute $k'(t)$ if $k(t)=\\frac{1}{\\sqrt[3]{3t}}+\\left(\\frac{t-8}{7}\\right)^3$.",
  "answer": "\\frac{1}{\\sqrt[3]{3}}(-1/3)t^{-4/3}+3/7\\left(\\frac{t-8}{7}\\right)^2)",
  "ivar": "t"
},

{
  "question": "Compute $f'(x)$ if $f(x)=\\frac{x^{1/5}}{\\sqrt{2}}+6e^x+\\pi^2$.",
  "answer": "1/5 x^{-4/5}/\\sqrt{2}+6e^x",
  "ivar": "x"
},

{
  "question": "Compute $f'(t)$ if $f(t)=\\sqrt{t+\\tan(\\pi t)}$.",
  "answer": "\\frac{1}{2}\\frac{1}{\\sqrt{t+\\tan(\\pi t)}}(1+\\pi\\sec^2(\\pi t))",
  "ivar": "t"
},

{
  "question": "Compute $G'(x)$ if $G(x)=\\frac{x^5-x^{3/2}+7}{\\sqrt{x}}$.",
  "answer": "\\frac{9}{2}x^{7/2}-1-\\frac{7}{2}x^{-3/2}",
  "ivar": "x"
},

{
  "question": "Compute $h'(z)$ if $h(z)=z\\ln(cz)+c^2$ where $c$ is a constant.",
  "answer": "\\ln(cz)+1",
  "ivar": "z",
  "const": "c"
},

{
  "question": "Compute $f'(v)$ where $f(v)=\\arcsin(\\sqrt{v})$",
  "answer": "\\frac{1}{\\sqrt{1-v}}\\frac{1}{2\\sqrt{v}}",
  "ivar": "v"
},

{
  "question": "Compute $f'(x)$ if $f(x)=(2x+1)\\tan(x)\\ln(7x)$.",
  "answer": "2\\tan(x)\\ln(7x)+(2x+1)\\cdot(\\sec^2(x)\\ln(7x)+\\tan(x)\\frac{1}{x})",
  "ivar": "x"
},

{
  "question": "Compute $F'(x)$ if $F(x)=\\frac{8}{\\tan(x)}$.",
  "answer": "-\\frac{8}{\\tan^2x}\\sec^2x",
  "ivar": "x"
},

{
  "question": "Compute $g'(t)$ if $g(t)=\\frac{1+e^t}{1+e^{-9t}}$.",
  "answer": "\\frac{e^t(1+e^{-9t})+9(1+e^t)e^{-9t}}{(1+e^{-9t})^2}",
  "ivar": "t"
},

{
  "question": "Compute $\\frac{dy}{dx}$ if $\\cos(x^2+y^2)=5xy$.",
  "answer": "-\\frac{\\sin(x^2+y^2)2x+5y}{\\sin(x^2+y^2)2y +5x}",
  "ivar": "x",
  "const": "y"
}

]
} 